goals big or small we Finance them all
at ICA home finance our aim is to make
the goals of our customers come true
whether it is buying the dream home or
making a business investment we are
always there to help when it comes to
Housing Finance we offer end to-end
Solutions right from home search that
helps you find your dream home to home
loans that help you realize your dream
with pradhanmantri AAS yoga we affirm
our commitment to offer affordable
housing to our customers we help our
customers in their time of financial
needs with products like go loans and
Loan against
property to meet their investment goal
we offer fixed deposits which are rated
by Crystle as flea stable we are working
continuously towards our goal of
ensuring 72-hour disbursement in home
loans our 1600 plus employees spread
across 140 branches are working
tirelessly to make the dreams of our
customers come true
[Music]